Md. Jahangir Hossein

Software Engineer

Python developer with 1+ years of experience executing data-driven solutions to increase efficiency, accuracy, and utility of internal data processing. Experienced at creating data regression models, using predictive data modeling, and analyzing ML/DL algorithms to deliver insights and implement action- oriented solutions.



jahangir.hossein@devnetlimited.com

01701022895

Dhaka, Bangladesh 👂

www.j4h2ir.com

linkedin.com/in/jahangir-hossein in

github.com/cloudy4next 🜎

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software EngineerDevnet Limited

10/2020 - Present

Tasks

 AI proctoring For Transparency International Bangladesh (TIB)

Web Developer

PentesterSpace Limited | Cyber Security Solution Provider

06/2019 - 10/2020

Cheif Executive of Research and Development.

Bauet Computer Society

04/2020 - Present

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in CSE

Bangladesh Army University of Engineering and Technology

03/2017 - Present

Thesis

 Toon-gan for generating Bangla animation Image.

SKILLS

Python Tensorflo

Pytorch

Django

AWS

Laravel/Django

Docker

Linux

Sql/NoSql

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Diaper Shop (08/2020 - 10/2020)

A e-commerce based online Diaper Shop

ATM management system (03/2019 - 03/2019)

- A Java Based ATM Management system for University

Cone Detection (02/2021 - Present)

- Traffic Cone detection for automation Car

Covid-19 Scanner (04/2020 - 05/2020)

X-ray based Covid Detection

PUBLICATION

Recognition of Bengali Sign Language using Novel Deep Convolutional Neural Network

DOI: 10.1109/STI50764.2020.9350418

Classification of Bengali Handwritter Multiclass characters using Novel Deep Neural Nets. (01/2021 - Present)

Proposed a journal on Springer.

LANGUAGES

Bangla

Enalis

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Travel

Books

Blogging